gotchosen.com 2012-09-09

# Privacy Policy | GotChosen: $40K To Give Away!

Gotchosen, Inc. ("Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of our Scholarship Drawing Participants’ personal information. This statement applies with respect to the information that we collect from the Company web site, located at http://www.gotchosen.com. Amendments to this statement will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. 

By completing and submitting your entry form to GotChosen, Inc., you signify your agreement to our privacy policy.  If you do not accept this privacy policy, please do not enter the scholarship drawing online or through the mail.  This policy and our legal obligations under this policy are subject to the laws of Florida and the United States of America, despite the location of the user.

Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.

**I. INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through your IP address, computer settings or most-recently visited URL.

In addition, for your scholarship drawing entry we will ask you to provide certain identifiable information about yourself such as your name, age, e-mail address, zip code, telephone number, and state. You are allowing us to share this information by providing it.  Please see the next section (USE OF INFORMATION) for details regarding what we do with this information. Your **** referred friends and family must voluntarily consent to these terms of use prior to GotChosen accepting additional entries on your behalf.

**II. USE OF INFORMATION**

We will send Entrants a confirmation e-mail when they register for our drawing/sweepstakes. These confirmation e-mails are not promotional in nature and the user may not opt-out of receiving these confirmation e-mails. If you withdraw your entry and no longer wish to receive such correspondence you may always follow the unsubscribe procedures which will be found within the commercial e-mails received from http://www.gotchosen.com, our affiliates and marketing partners. You may also contact http://www.gotchosen.com either through our “Contact Us” page or by writing directly to us at: info@gotchosen.com.

Non-personal demographic and profile data is used to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content we think you might be interested in. This information may also be shared with advertisers on an aggregate non-personal basis.

We do not rent, license, or sell personal data to third parties unless permission is granted through user submission of the checked permission notice box appearing at the registration and entry page of http://www.gotchosen.com. In the event of a merger, acquisition, or change of control of GotChosen, customer data would be considered a business asset and would be transferred. We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose personal information as required by law or to protect the safety and security of our users.

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

**III. USE OF IP ADDRESSES**

We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

**IV. USE OF COOKIES**

When you view our Web site we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. Rather, they help you navigate a Web site as easily as possible. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to prevent you from reentering all your registration data at each connection.

We use an outside advertisement server company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. The advertisement server company may collect cookies received with outside banner ads. We do not have access to information that would confirm the use of cookies by the advertisement server company.

**V. SECURITY**

Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information.

**VI. OTHER WEB SITES; LINKS**

Our Web site contains links to other Web sites. GotChosen, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**VII. CORRECT; UPDATE**

GotChosen, Inc. allows its users the option to change or modify information previously provided. This may be done by visiting the site, making the desired changes, and then saving the profile.

Unfortunately, to the extent that such information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will reach the other databases. We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is removed from or corrected in our records.

**VIII. CHOICE; OPT OUT**

You may opt-out of receiving promotional **** communications from our partners, and from us, by visiting the Profile Page on the GotChosen website and following the appropriate instructions.

**IX. PUBLIC FORUMS**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**X.   CHILDREN**

Only persons age 18 and older may register for the site and no unregistered individuals should access the site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under the age of 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible. 

**Contacting us:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at info@gotchosen.com.
